Joachim Skog Sætre

Symreveien 24, 1406 Ski +47 47605059 | jokke90@gmail.com Born: 20. februar 1990

I am 29 years old and live in Ski (Norway). I talk and write fluent Norwegian and English.

I have worked my way up the grocery store industry and have operated a shop with a turnover of about NOK 60 million.

Now I am studying Front End development at Noroff Vocational School, The program is finished in the spring of 2020. I am a curious and teachable person, who is dedicated to doing well in my workplace. I look at myself as an outgoing introvert who is sociable, while at the same time prefer to spend time in my own company.

Friends and colleagues describe me as faithful, honest, straightforward, effective and reliable. These are the qualities I bring with me into the workplace.

Work experience

01.2017 – d.d	Store Clerk, Kiwi Finstad
	Finstad Mat AS
08.2015 - 01.2017	Store Manager, Kiwi Mysen
	Kiwi Norge
01.2015 - 08.2015	Assistant Store Manager, Kiwi Fagerstrand
	Kiwi Norge
08.2014 - 01.2015	Store Manager Trainee, Kiwi Sletta
	Sletta drift AS
10.2006 - 08.2014	Store Clerk, Kiwi Finstad
	Finstad mat AS

Education

08.2018 - D.D	Front End Development, Noroff Fagskole
08.2017 - 06.2018	Digital Forensics, Noroff University
08.2009 - 06.2010	Salg & Service, Drømtorp VGS
08.2008 - 06.2009	Salg & Service, Drømtorp VGS
08.2006 - 06.2007	Elektro, ÅS VGS

Other

Språk Norwegian: Mother Tongue English: written and verbally

References

Contact me for references